RESUME OBJECTIVE

I am a Web Master, Network Engineer & Graphic; Technology has been always my interest. The way world is moving fast with technology and I really want to do my part by solving problems using technology. Mobile application, Web development and Graphic design are my professional sectors.

EXPERIENCE

JOURNALIST

Niboye Sector (December 2019 - Current)

• News reporter and communicator.

ADMINISTRATOR ANALYST & SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Kicukiro Primary and Secondary school (September 2020- December 2020)

- Provided oversight to the personal team, discussed project roadblocks to promote issue resolution and ensured the use of best practices.
- Consulted with network engineering staff to evaluate hardware and software requirements for new system development.
- Implemented and tested enhancement feature requests to improve product functionality and extend performance.

FRONT END DEVELOPER [Intern]

AFRO ARK (June 2020- August 2020)

- Program, test and debug all web applications.
- Design, develop, test and deploy web applications.
- Code pages, files, test, debug and deploy.
- Develop appropriate code structures to solve specific tasks.

CLASS REPRESENTATIVE

Davis college Akilah Campus (September 2019- December 2019)

- Represent the class in some events.
- Solving class problems.
- Communicating information from staff to students and also from students to staff.

CERTIFICATES

- Cisco Networking IT Essentials certificate.
- Graphic design certificate from WDA.
- Certificate in using Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel and Microsoft PowerPoint.
- Advanced certificate from REB.
- Responsive Web Design from FreecodeCamp.
- Diploma in Information System
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures from FreecodeCamp
- (CAMLA EPT TEST) Cambridge Michigan Language Assessment English Placement Test
- CCNA I&II

CONTACT

Email:

fabiennehirwa1@gmail.com

Phone: +250780577060

SOCIAL MEDIA



www.linkedin.com/in/fa bienne-hirwa

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Team Collaboration and Leadership skills
- Strong Work Ethic
- Time Management
- Handling Pressure
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Java, C++, PHP, React.js, Node.js and SQL, Visual Basic, MySql, wordpress, wix, Bootstrap and Microsoft office.
- Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Information Technology

University of Kigali

Current

Davis college

Diploma in Information System

2018 - 2021

PORTFOLIO LINK

fabiennehirwa1.wixsite.com/portfolio

REFERENCES

Rusimbi Patrick

IT Manager at AFRO ARK **Tel:** +250789471282

rusimbipatrick@outlook.com